这些是content provider所需求的功能
These are the required content provider functions. You
你可以以任何你喜欢的方式实现它们
can implement them any way you like, but
但是你会发现将它们在SQLite 数据库的顶部实现
you'll find that it's really straight forward to
是非常直接的方法
implement them on top of a SQLite database. The
content provider函数中包含的参数
parameters packed into our content provider functions match
和Android中SQLite的接口参数是准确配对的
the parameters used for Android's SQLite's interface almost
最大的不同就是我们使用URI代替了
exactly. The biggest difference is that we replaced
table string。在最简单的content provider的实现中
the table string, with a uri. In the simplest
数据查询被直接
content provider implementation, the query is passed
传送到数据库中，注意，
straight through to the database. Note that
有一些参数并不能简单地通过content provider控制
there are parameters that cannot be easily
比如说，grouping functionality
controlled through content providers, such as grouping functionality.
但是这个参数允许灵活使用
But the interface allows for very flexible querying.
更重要的是，projection或者columns
Most importantly, the projection or columns allows for querying
使得查询变得更加高效，因为column 索引和cursor object
to be much more efficient. Because the column
是与我们提交到数据库中
indices and our cursor object match the projection that
的projection相互对应的，我们可以
we submit to the database, we can just
通过数字索引得到它们的值，而不需要
get the values by their numerical index instead of
使用 getColumnIndex去寻找每一个
having to use getColumnIndex to look up each
column 索引。好的，现在是时候编写一些有关Sunshine应用的代码了
column index. All right, it's time to code some
让我们写一个content provider
more Sunshine. Let's code a content provider.